What I just said was to refute him.
I didn't mean anything else.
Really?
Really.
Okay, but I'm sick now.
I need you to wipe my body.
It's not like you're too sick
to lift your arms.
It's not like you haven't
touched it before.
Don't let your hands shake.
I say, girl,
wiping here,
are you trying to make
something happen with me?
Ah, no,
I didn't mean to.
That's about it.
I'm leaving.
Trying to run after starting a fire?
Ah!
Mister, I'll go brew your medicine first.
Blushing like this.
Could it be...
Hey, wild girl,
there's something I need to make clear.
My father saved
the Sect Leader's life back then.
Before he died,
the Sect Leader promised
to marry me to repay the favor.
You'd better watch yourself.
He has a fiancée?
Then just now he...
Madam, the medicine is ready.
The Sect Leader asked you
to deliver it quickly.
I got it.
He has a fiancée
but still allows others to call me Madam.
Sect Leader, be gentle.
You're hurting me.
Oh,
then I'll stop.
No.
Asking me to deliver
the medicine personally
just for this scene.
A wild girl indeed.
She can't even see through
an auditory illusion.
Bai Ze of Yungong Pavilion
really did me a big favor.
With the wild girl taken away by him,
the Sect Leader is all mine.
Sect Leader,
I'm here to deliver the medicine.
Why is it you?
Where is A Kong?
She left the medicine bowl at the door
and left with a man.
It seemed to be Bai Ze.
What did you say?
Auditory illusion.
You'd better pray nothing happened to her.
Mr. Bai,
what exactly do you want from me?
Didn't you say you wanted
to leave Young Master Yan?
I happen to need a wife.
Why don't you marry me?
What nonsense are you talking about?
After we get married, we'll live here.
I'll take care of you,
and you'll plow the fields, weave,
carry water, and water the garden.
There should be a limit
to being shameless, hey!
I want to support myself.
Do you know where I can make money?
Make money?
Qiong City, of course.
Qiong City?
But the Qi residence is also there.
Afraid of running into your old flame?
I told you to just marry me.
Let's go.
To Qiong City.
It's a medical bounty posted
by the Shangguan family.
A medical bounty?
Little one.
You know medicine, right?
Just a little.
I wouldn't dare take the notice.
Ah!
Who took the notice?
Was it this lady?
Bai Ze,
just you wait!